I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Oh.
Let it!
What was that?
Ellie, did you hear that?
I heard it, Manny.
Whatever it is, it's miles away.
Pictures, you all right?
Where is she?
No teenagers ever up early.
Well, easy wooden.
She's not on lockdown.
You two were supposed
to be responsible uncles.
What?
I didn't see a piece of sneak
off maybe 15, 20 minutes ago.
Where did she went with Louis to the falls?
The falls?
Where did the delinquents go?
Relax, it's just where the kids hang in.
No, no, it's a gateway hangout.
First it's the falls, then
she's Peterson, her trunk,
and the next thing you know,
she's addicted to berries.
Annie, you are overreacting.
She's not gonna be
your little girl forever.
I know.
That's what worries me.
Come on!
Whoa!
What did you get your head out of the ground
for once and try to have a little fun?
I'm a mole hog.
My head's supposed to be
underground, and my idea of fun
isn't risking death so that you
can meet some cute mammoth.
Ethan isn't cute?
He's hot.
Besides, you can't spend
your whole life playing it safe.
I know I would.
Dad?
There's no reason to be mad.
You know how I feel about you
going to the falls, especially alone.
She's not alone, sir.
You don't count, Wiener.
Yes, there's my place.
And you just put me in.
I thank you.
Come on, young lady.
We're going home where
I can keep an eye on you.
Should I just wait here or...
Yeah, you don't scare me, mother nature.
There's nothing you can
throw at me that I can't handle.
Yeah.
I think we're almost there.
Wait better be.
I just lost the steering.
Have any more sane questions?
It's our feeding time.
Mom, Granny's talking
about our dead pet again.
Hey, boss off, everybody.
Off, down, on the police.
That is massive.
I hurt somebody.
Oh!
Okay, so tell me, when exactly will
I be allowed to hang out with boys?
When I'm dead, plus three
days, just to make sure I'm dead.
Manny, are you okay?
Get off my face.
That was fun.
Now, who should I eat first?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, that really be you.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Mom!
Dad!
For sure!
Hey!
Granny?
This pump is ripe, but take it!
Oh, my whole familiar!
See?
He still hugs his parents.
I never thought I'd
see my little baby again.
We've been searching everywhere for you.
You have?
I knew it, I knew it, deep down.
I knew I wasn't a bad dude.
Oh, that's incorrect.
We totally abandoned you.
But?
Oh, isn't it?
I missed you.
Oh, right?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And we just knew Sid would want to
see his poor dear Dranny before him.
Her time is up.
Oh, Barry, you're all
a dassel, you'll agree.
So frail.
And she can't wait to
spend time with you, Sid.
Oh, yeah.
Granny.
I never get to have any fun.
Why don't you show her your cave?
Yeah, she could use a nap.
Boy, there's so much to tell you.
You know, a lot has happened
since the last time I saw you.
Not interested.
But we fought diamond
swords in the ice days.
We didn't make sense for children.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, you can't just leave.
It'll be crushed.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Sorry, Cookie, things are
breaking a pod back off.
Oh, we're headed inland,
and Kranny is just dead weight.
See ya!
And war the community!
She tensed the water!
Well, that explains a lot about Sid.
Mom, Dad, you have Danny's teach.
Can't find him.
Hey!
Can you chew this thing for me?
Guys?
Where is everyone?
I'll handle this.
Sid, you family was
wiped out by an asteroid.
Sorry.
What?
What Diego is trying to say is they left.
They only wanted to find you
so you could take care of Granny.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
I mean, what kind of sick family would
ditch their old granny out somewhat?
That's just crazy.
That's just my family.
At least you still have Granny.
Right, buddy?
Yeah, Granny.
Granny?
Wow.
For an old girl, she moves fast.
Granny!
Come on, come out wherever you are.
Come on, Granny.
Here, Granny, Granny, Granny, Granny.
I have prunes for ya.
Just the way you like them.
Oh no.
What if your dad finds out?
I'm not as tough as I look.
Wait, did you hear that?
Ah!
Hey, look.
There's Ethan.
Yeah, Ethan!
He's called boy.
Yeah!
See?
Fun.
No danger.
Woo-hoo!
Check me out!
Sure he's fine.
Oh, you did not just do that.
That was crazy.
Nice.
Isn't he perfect?
Perfect.
Yeah, it's not such a strong word.
Maybe adequate.
Gooey's talking.
Is he even?
I bet it's Ethan.
Oh, hey, we know.
What are you guys doing here?
Many told us to keep an eye on you.
But not to let you see it
under any circumstances.
Okay, I'm going forward.
Do I look okay?
Louis?
Okay, doesn't even begin to cover it.
Oh, Louis, you're the greatest friend ever.
That's me.
Hi, Ethan.
My name's Peaches.
What's yours?
What am I doing?
Okay, just be cool.
Just be cool.
That's intense.
Ow, ow, this hurts so much!
No, no!
Brose, is that where all
who chills were past them?
Oh, what just happened?
Oh, no.
Even I am so sorry.
I... Wow.
Even better looking up close, phenomenal.
I mean... You have a twin sister.
Am I interrupting something?
Dad!
Oh, boy.
Okay, I... I just...
No, no, you left.
Move back a bit closer.
You, keep away from my daughter.
Dad, no.
And you, you're grounded.
But I didn't.
Grounded.
Loser alert.
Oh, but you're dead.
Seriously, that's embarrassing.
What a freak.
Peaches.
Peaches, come on.
Let's talk about this.
How could you embarrass
me in front of my friends?
You deliberately went where
you weren't supposed to.
Oh, you can't control my life.
I'm trying to protect you.
That's what fathers do.
Well, I wish you weren't my father.
She's just upset, honey.
Pages, it's not the end of the world.
Whoa, excuse me.
I don't think that was you.
Uh, what was that?
I don't know.
Stay there.
I'll come to you.
Yeah!
He just kicked back!
Whoa!
Hurry, dad!
Hurry!
Manny!
Whoa!
Yeah, go!
Never would have made it.
Go to the land bridge!
You'll be safe on the other side!
No, many no!
Help me do that!
No!
Help me!
You have to get out of here!
No!
Go now!
Whoa!
Get back!
No matter how long
it takes, I will find you.
Mom, this is all my fault.
If I had just pitches, this
is not your fault, okay?
What if I never see him again?
And the last thing we did was fight.
Hey, your father is the toughest,
most stubborn man that I've ever met.
He'll come back for us.
That's a promise.
Come on!
Help me turn this thing around!
Everyone, please!
I'm so down!
Don't panic!
Wait, Mom, where's Louis?
We have to find him.
Okay, fast.
They need me!
You gotta get back!
Buddy, this thing's too big to turn.
The current's pulling us out.
You know, my mother was telling me that
bad news was just good news in disguise.
Was this before she abandoned you?
Yes, it was.
But the point thing,
that even though things
look bad, there's a rainbow
around every corner.
And nothing but food set.
We know.
Louis, where are you?
Come on, we have to go.
Louis?
Ages.
Louis, you have to jump.
No, no, save yourselves.
We're not leaving without you.
Oh, thank goodness.
Jump.
Thanks for coming back.
What do you mean?
You don't leave a friend behind.
Great.
Let's go.
That wall is going to
keep moving and crush us.
We need to get to the land bridge.
Any questions?
Yes?
Will you drink water through your trunk?
Does it taste like buggers?
Uh, no.
Well, sometimes.
Let's move.
Keep your eye on the horizon!
I can't find the horizon!
Hold me.
If I don't make it, find me
a wife to tell her I love her.
We made it.
Come on, ocean fish.
That's the fish you can do.
Am I right, buddy?
There really is a rainbow
around every corner.
You okay?
I'm just so worried about my dad.
Listen, we're gonna get to him.
At this pace we'll stay
ahead of the wall and
we'll make it to the
landbridge before you know it.
We're all gonna survive this.
Okay, maybe day won't,
but everyone else totally fine.
Still heading away from home.
Yeah, but we survived
and we still have each other.
Thanks to me worse, right?
For once, he's actually right.
We made it through storms and tidal
waves and a vicious assortment of seafood.
What more can they hit us with?
Ow!
Get up, I don't wanna get up.
I wanna get up, I wanna
get up, I wanna get up.
I'm trying to sleep.
Granny, you're alive.
And can we say how
thrilled we are to see you?
Hey, Fitts, you want to get me out of here?
Whoa!
Hey!
We're taking out my dessert.
That's your motivation.
I can't believe this.
You slept through that storm.
Yeah, I slept through the
comet that killed the unicorns.
Thanks for drawing my pants, Sydney.
Granny, grab my palm.
No way.
This is my first bath in decades.
There's your proof.
Quick, somebody do something.
I got you, Granny.
Get off of me.
Ow, ow, ow, ow.
Ready?
What are you peeping times all looking at?
Lady can't take a bath in peace?
I ballin' me like a rock ropes.
What's the life expectancy
for a female sloth?
Oh, she'll outlive us
all, you know that, right?
Yeah, the spiteful ones live the waters.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
And you'll get me!
Oh!
How big is this ocean?
Water.
Everywhere.
No, I need to drop a key drink.
Well, except maybe that drops.
That's a little salty.
Mommy's calling you!
Fresh ass!
Poppy, sweetie!
Hey, lady, have you seen pressure?
If you mean the imaginary
or perhaps deceased pet
that you keep searching
for it, no, I haven't.
Guys, look!
With his birds, this land, right?
Hey, buddy, come here!
No, wait, wait, come back!
Come back!
It's a huge bum team, Capitan.
Four passengers.
Right for the taking.
One very smelly and one very plump.
In my ocean.
What a terrible turn of events.
I love a terrible turn of events.
Hahaha.
Am I hallucinating or is that
ice coming straight towards us?
Yeah, yeah, it's coming.
It sounds like there's animals on it.
Hey!
We're being nasty, we're being nasty.
I hear laughter.
Oh, must be a party cruise.
Whoo!
Hey, hey look, fluffy.
I'll get the big woolly one.
Wow.
Get ready to slice and dice, boys.
Suck it off, Squintay.
Wait for Captain's orders.
Oh, I'm down there.
How lucky are you?
You know, these waters
are infested with pirates.
Right, boys?
I had we found you before they did.
Captain Gut, here to help.
You know, that's a nice monkey.
Look, we don't want any trouble.
We just need to get back to the continent.
The continent?
That pile of rubble?
My family's there.
So if you could just... Oh, your family.
That is so sweet.
I hope you said goodbye.
Because there's no way back.
Yes, there is.
Don't you remember, Captain?
You can sound to switch back
COVID and catch a car back from there.
Look, I still trapped this nugget is.
Thank you, Mr. Flynn.
How?
See, I knew there was a way home.
There is no home.
And here, your ship belongs to me.
Battle station!
Fire!
Why the colors?
Now surrender your ship or face my fury.
Or face your furry what?
Not furry.
Fury!
Fire!
Fire the starboard, can it?
I love this job!
Shira, fetch.
I, I, Captain.
You almost made it.
I don't fight girls.
I can see why.
I like that.
Let's rumpa tiny.
Lights out, big fella.
Hey buddy, welcome to the party.
Let's see what kind of moves you got.
Oh, look at him!
Where's my booty?
Has anyone seen it?
Good!
It's a night behind you!
Where's my booty?
I can't see him!
Look!
It's all I can see.
This is a lovely vacation.
Best out of the head.
Morning sunshine!
Let me be the first to
extend the hand of friendship.
That's your foot.
Nothing gets by you, does it?
What do you want?
I bet you're feeling lost.
Scared, confused.
Allow me to explain.
Help me out, boys.
Oh!
Captain, can a sing a shunt in?
Here you are on a boat.
You're a trip.
You're a float when might
even say you're stuck.
Well, I don't want to glow,
but I would like to note that.
Or a love.
You can save by the ape
that rules these waters.
So forget about your wives and daughters.
First mate, introduce me to them.
I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I, I,
I'm a primate pirate, pioneer, and
these are my brave fucking ears.
All of whom were once lost souls like you.
It's true.
He'd ask you that.
He saved her butts.
But that we owe our lives to gut
and assume he doesn't kill him.
You would own him.
Kill them.
Me?
No, no.
Well, at least not this very
large, useful, mammoth.
It hands off.
Anyway.
Here we are on a ship moving at quite
a cliff through the ever-shifting ice.
Come along on the trip, train.
That's a pit.
That's good at fucks.
In a world that's so we wonder.
To survive, you must learn to ponder.
Luckily, that's my field of expertise.
He's the best.
He's a rock.
We really should be leaving.
We got a good going.
Lots laying.
All right, we should be staying.
Undisputed.
That's me.
Let me give you a visual aid.
I just gently press here.
And go down.
And then you're entered.
Come here out.
I still don't get it.
Look, as much as I'm
tempted to join a monkey,
the Easter Bunny, and
a giant bag of pudding.
I'll pass.
No one's gonna stop me
from getting back to my family.
That family is going
to be the death of you.
First mate, Judas and the deadweight.
I answer, prepare the plank.
Preparing the plank.
You want me to walk into the water?
I can't, because I just ate less than
20 minutes ago, and you know the rule.
That's a miss.
Oh, OK. Long as it's safe.
Wait.
Oh, thank goodness.
Stump the wench, too.
Ah!
Ladies first.
Such a nice boy.
Why can't you be more like him, Sidney?
Granny, no, wait.
Manie, get me to the vine.
Yeah, yeah, got it.
Y'all got some lovely gold fish.
Come on, a little more.
No.
It stinks that mammoth!
Come on, baby!
Kick it, monkey, buck!
And look at you!
11 tons of land lover blood!
Hey, I'm not fat!
I'm hoofy, too bad, Tubby!
I could have used you!
Ain't gonna happen, Captain!
I got you, Daddy!
Get me up!
Let's go!
Ow!
Everyone have to notice!
No!
My bounty!
Uh-huh!
It's some kind of battle ship!
What are we gonna do?
We're all gonna drown!
Uh-huh!
You're a sea creature, you idiot!
Oh!
Good points!
Should I stay the weight, Captain?
No!
Wait!
What about Shira?
What about her?
Yeah.
Anyone else want to play Captain?
Good.
Now, come on, clever brain.
Swim!
God, Flynn, anyone there?
Here, grab home.
No, go away.
I'd rather drown.
Whatever the lady wants.
I said I didn't need your help.
You're welcome.
So, care to join our scurvy crew.
You guys are like the start of a bad joke.
And we saved you.
That makes you the punchline, Kitty.
Don't.
Call me, Kitty.
Okay, I won't.
Kitty.
If they kiss, I'm gonna puke.
What?
Wait, no.
Maybe we should rest for a few hours.
I miss you, Dad.
Well that's something
you don't see every day.
I've never seen a mam asleep like that.
Whatever.
Okay, that's a little weird.
So, how you doing?
You know, with all of this.
Honestly?
A little scared.
Okay, a lot scared.
Everything we knew was gone.
Yeah, I was pretty scared too.
I mean, not scared, you
know, like, concerned.
Hey, uh, do you want to
walk with me tomorrow?
Try and get our minds off all this stuff.
You want to walk with me?
Well, you did almost
flatten me this morning, so I
figure it can't really go
worse than that, right?
Yeah.
Oh, just one thing.
Totally no big deal, but you
might want to lose the Mohawk.
Lewis?
Yeah, sure.
Not a problem.
Oh, wow.
Someone looks happy.
Ethan's great, isn't he?
Baby, I know you like this one, but just
don't let anyone change who you are, okay?
I know.
You coming up?
I think I'm gonna sleep down here tonight.
Okay.
Night, baby.
Night, mom.
Night, dad.
Hey, you're the sandwich for me.
Granny, why didn't our family want us?
What's wrong with us?
Dad, I think we'll screw up,
and we can't do anything right.
It's a rat!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Screw up!
Oh, sad!
Ow!
Never make it home on this thing.
Oh, well, maybe you should have thought of
that before you capsized our burg genius.
Yeah, trying to escape.
Win, try, baby.
Yeah, land.
Wait, what?
Not her.
There!
Huh?
Land!
Food!
Oh, I missed you so much!
Look at me!
I brushed it away!
Okay, snack time's over.
We got to build a raft.
Man, he... Wow!
Sheeram must really hate building rafts.
Go get her!
She can help us get back!
Sheeram!
Let go of me.
Where do you think you're going?
Whoa.
Switch back home.
It's the way home.
No.
You call this a ship, you miserable runs!
Yeah, you little ruts!
Get to work!
Faster!
Worthless worthy!
Sons of Sikes Goose's
first shark bait wave-offs!
What did he say?
Oh.
Now get this chunk of ice seaworthy by
sundown, where I will kill the lot of you!
So, what do you think?
Two words.
Anger management.
How?
I'm talking about the current.
The ego's right.
We found the way home.
Yeah, that's great.
Too bad we don't have a ship.
Sure we do.
It's right there.
Well, that's a flawless plan.
You want to pirate a
pirate ship from pirates?
It pains me to say this,
but our prisoner has a point.
Yeah, well...
Wait a minute.
Maybe we can help each other.
Hey, little fellas.
Hey, come on out.
No, no, no, no, it's okay.
We're not gonna hurt you.
How about you and us
against the pirates, huh?
You got no idea what I'm saying, do you?
Okay, uh, ship.
Me want.
Yeah, nice try, jungle Jim.
Now go ahead, make fun.
Okay, he got it.
Oh, he did.
Oh, uh, uh, thank you.
Uh, may I try?
Yeah, knock yourself out.
Okay, watch this.
And me, me, me, me, me, me.
Six lost, six lost, six lost.
That they got.
They're in.
Great.
We'll free your buddies, and we can all
work together to kick a little pirate booty.
Easy, Kitty.
Water.
You need it.
I don't need anything from you.
Fine, die a thirst.
That'll really show me.
Wait.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
You know, you have a way of saying thank
you that makes it sound like drop dead.
It's a gift.
Well, you're pretty soft, her saber.
Excuse me, I am not soft.
Okay, I happen to be
a remorseless assassin.
Yeah, go poo.
Hey, I made you another call necklace.
He keeps losing them.
I think I'm starting to get
while you're not in a pack.
Listen, I chose to
leave my pack, all right?
Congratulations, Warrior Princess.
So did I.
Really?
What?
Nothing, I just, I know how hard that is.
Walking away from everything you know.
Oh great, what are we gonna
braid each other's fur now?
Funny.
Really funny.
Can I tell you the difference
between you and me?
I wouldn't still be wearing that necklace?
No.
We both might have
wanted out of pack life, but
at least I didn't trade
one pack for another.
I got something more.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
A herd.
What's the difference?
We have each other's backs.
God has my back on his first mate.
Really?
Because I don't see guts ending
on any search parties for you.
You know you won't beat him.
You big furry friend over there?
He has no idea what he's up against.
Yeah, but neither does he got.
Okay, we need precision timing
from everyone to get that ship.
Have fun.
We've got your end covered, right?
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
Here you go.
How free is little friends?
Sit and granny?
Sir!
Untie the ship, sir!
Right.
Unwind the vines.
Don't let go until we're all on board.
We're relying on you, Sid.
You got that?
Oh, yes, sir.
Totally focused, sir.
Don't worry.
It'll be easy, since we don't
have the guards here anymore.
We need to move.
Now, sprinted back down the hatches.
Rise, hoist the anger, and Gupta.
Why the color?
The thoughts, Captain.
We're sent sail for vengeance, lads.
Ooh, a love vengeance.
Captain.
Shira.
Oh, what a relief.
I thought we lost you.
The mammoth.
He washed a short with me.
He's here.
Did you sink your fangs into him?
Did he beg for his life?
No.
The saber took me to hell.
You're a failure.
I need warriors.
And all I have are kitty
cats and bunny rabbits.
And a seal and a kangaroo.
You take the saber down, or you die trying.
No excuses.
Yes, Captain.
Mr. Scrantchett.
I, sir?
Your first mate now.
Yo, ho, ho, in a bottle
of cool with me, Captain.
I'm always saber.
You answer to me, though.
Got, listen.
He's coming for the-
Grab your weapons, mates!
At the spoon, Flynn!
Follow me!
Guys, it's not necessary.
Really?
I love you too, yeah.
unwind the vine.
Don't let go unwind the vine.
Don't let go.
Oh, yumbo.
Yeah.
Oh, zit.
No.
It's a lotus, Barry.
It'll paralyze you.
Oh, please.
I know my berries.
Don't swallow.
Yeah, fine.
If there's one thing I know,
Oh, no!
It's better diversion!
I know!
I'm having a blast!
Nope!
Pinhead's too!
You're stealing my ship!
One thing, Sid, you couldn't do one thing?
Look at you.
Sid, can you hear me?
Baba!
Say something, buddy.
Oh!
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
We got to catch it
before it hits open water.
Sorry.
All right.
I'll hold you higher.
Sorry.
All right.
Sorry, buddy Sorry, buddy
I'm coming for you, man.
Come on!
Why are you doing this?
You don't understand.
I don't have a choice.
You don't have to live this way, Shira.
You'll be safe with us.
We take care of each other.
Diego!
I can't hold that much longer!
Come with us.
Come with me.
What are you doing?
I've got your back.
So long we've had a breath.
Thanks, Father Chef.
Oh, there he is.
Sure leaves over.
Get your sorry carcasses on board now.
God, I can explain.
When this ends, I'll have a
tiger's skin hanging on my wall.
I don't care who's...
That man has taken my
ship, my bounty, and
now the loyalty of my crew.
I will destroy him at everything he loves.
Thank you.
Wait for it!
That was awesome!
Can I ask you guys something?
How are you both so happy?
Doesn't it weigh on you that
the world might be ending?
Can I tell them our secret?
Come here, come here.
We're very, very stupid.
But still you're not a teensy bit
concerned about I don't know say
imminent death I'm gonna go find
peaches Hey guys over here come on.
It's a shortcut
You're gonna love this.
Come on, girls.
I love them a lot.
Wow.
This is so cool.
It's like we're actually down.
That is amazing.
Echo!
Too bad your Mohawk friend is in here, huh?
You're not really friends
with him, are you?
Yeah, come clean, peaches.
Oh, you friends with that walk
with a little rodent one night.
I mean, Louis and I,
we've hung out or whatever.
But no, we're not really friends friends.
Not friends?
Louis, I busted.
And me.
Good to know.
Louis, wait!
He even runs away like a loser.
Whoa, peaches.
Don't stress.
You're with us now.
Yeah, stress is so stressful.
Yeah, girl, if you want to stress
about something, stress about your hair.
Guys, we should get out of here.
Are you kidding?
This is epic!
Six was that.
Yo, that was insane.
Hey, Beach.
Loosen up.
Have some fun.
Fun?
You call that fun?
I'm out of here.
Come on.
I mean, do you really
want to go back to hanging
with a weird Mohawk, a
week, and give all of this up?
I mean, it's bad enough that
your families have possible.
Bad enough.
There is nothing bad about
being part of my family.
I'd like hanging by my tail.
And if your genius is our normal,
the species is going to end up extinct.
Uh, yeah?
Well, your species is
going to be extinct first.
Burn!
We're the same species, genius.
What?
Double burn!
Hey, I can wiggle my show again.
The important one, the little
piggy who went to market.
Wait, I'm talking to that.
Oh, I had so many
things trapped inside of me
that I couldn't say
like, hey, I'm not dead.
Hey, why doesn't Hurricane
have an eye, but not in the air?
I'll push them over, boy.
You guys say it was an accident.
I'm in.
How about you, Diego?
There you go!
Hey, relax buddy!
Captain Crazy and his
floating petting zoo are history!
Come on!
We're finally heading home!
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I can't eat, can't sleep.
Maybe I'm coming down with something.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, I know what you've got.
The L-word.
Yeah, leprosy.
No, Sid, no, it's fall letters.
Starts with L, ends with E.
Aha!
Nice!
No!
Diego, my friend, is in love.
Oh, yeah!
Love!
You mean with the pirates?
No.
Oh, Sierra's got none to your skin.
Come on, admit it.
A rugged saber like you.
A more rugged saber like her.
No, no, no.
You guys are dead wrong.
You're in love, pussycats.
Yeah, go in, Sarah, sitting in a tree.
K-I-S-I-G. Real mature, guys.
Real mature, guys.
Real mature.
Cheer up.
I wanted to come with you.
She's beautiful.
I adore Slough, who cares
nothing about personal hygiene.
That's me, baby.
Runny.
Come to me, Granny.
Well, hello.
They'll wrinkle your the resin.
They're sweeter than fruit.
Too granny like you.
Ranny like you very much.
Guys, guys, aren't you paying attention?
Are you there?
Ellie?
We're over here, man.
This way, Daddy.
I really need you.
I know, honey.
Stay there.
I'm coming!
You were right, man.
You're always right.
No, no, look, I
wouldn't... Wait a minute.
Ellie would never say that.
Nanny?
No, no, they're not real.
They're monsters.
They're sirens.
Don't listen to them.
Who could take the sunrise?
No!
They may look real quick or not.
They're going to destroy the ship.
Come on, Tiger.
Swim with me.
Yeah.
I have a snack for you.
And she cooked too.
Said no.
Hmm.
Why are we guessing?
Um, because cruises are romantic?
Five more seconds, and
we'd have been gunners.
Call me.
Uh-uh.
Yeah.
Here, precious!
She thinks you finally found her pet.
Look, Granny, didn't you throw
imaginary foods to your imaginary pet?
Enough already.
We need to keep a lookout for home.
Ignore them, precious.
I do.
Can't take your eyes
off for for one minute.
Nope.
It's like having a child.
Only without any of the joy.
Hey, brain trust, race by impact.
Huh?
Well done.
Guys, look, we're almost home.
Buddy, I never doubted you.
Me either.
Well, except for the six or seven
times, I thought me were going to die.
What's wrong, sweetheart?
You ever say something you
knew you couldn't take back?
Is this about Lewis?
I messed it up so bad, mom.
It's okay.
It happens.
Cute boys can whiplash your brain.
No doubt about that.
But Ethan was the wrong guy.
And you figured it out.
You'll know what to say to Lewis.
What's going on?
The land bridge.
It's gone.
We're trapped!
But we were supposed to meet Dad here!
What are we gonna do?
Ellie!
Pages!
Oh, no.
Landbridge.
But if it's gone, then
how are we going to sit?
No.
They have to be on the other side.
Manny, there is no other side.
They have to be here.
Ellie!
Pages!
I'm here!
Please.
She's got to be here.
Wait, wait, did you hear that?
No, I heard something.
I heard it!
Is that pictures?
There she is!
Yeah!
We're coming, sweetie!
Don't move!
Daddy!
Pages!
Welcome home, Daddy.
Let's go with me.
What are the odds?
We were just talking about you.
You like the new ship?
I call her sweet revenge.
And look here.
We've got the catch to you.
Really?
I'm all right.
Let my daughter go.
It's OK.
He wants me.
And he's going to get me.
Sacrificing yourself for your daughter.
How touching.
How predictable.
Now, come and get her.
You remember us?
We're the bad guys.
All right.
Let them go.
I don't think so.
You destroyed everything I had.
I'm just returning the favor.
No!
I warned you.
Stop!
Let the mammoth go!
Weiner?
Uh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh-huh
Let's dance hero.
Don't stand there like barnacles!
Got him!
Bring some hand mike.
Aah!
That's your pet.
Maybe that crazy old
bat is not crazy after all.
No, she's not.
You ain't more formal
invitation, fancy paint.
I'm going to regret this.
Bottom of the way.
Be a scaredy cat.
This smells worse than me.
Brush us!
Sex and look was 45 degrees north.
Red is done running.
Back off.
It's okay.
I'm on your side.
No, you were a traitor.
Oh, you little bunny nose wiggles
in the cutest way when you're mad.
Fuck!
You're not lads, they're over kitty!
The silly rabbit?
Heracy does it.
Hey, that's not cool.
Come on.
Anyone have a body weight?
Something about a cup.
How's it looking?
Not good, Granny, sir.
This is so good!
And you missed the wild!
Hi, Mandy!
Sit!
Help!
No, Mandy!
I got your mother!
You stay there!
Hey back time!
It's dead.
No, it's too dangerous.
Not if you have possible.
She did it.
My daughter's all grown up.
That's my girl.
We need to get out of here.
Go, go, I'm right behind you.
No!
I'm right behind you.
Dad!
No!
There's no way to run, nanny!
Yeah!
You know, this ocean isn't
big enough for the bones of us.
Don't worry, you won't take up
much space once I've flattened you!
Oh!
Told you, Chubby, you shouldn't
have messed with the master of the sea.
You know, sometimes,
it pays to weigh 11 times!
No!
Unbelievable!
It won't be worth it!
So, you must be precious.
Mission accomplished, Granny.
Ha!
Who says old ladies can't drive?
That's me.
Let's roll the seas together.
I am.
How's that for an entrance?
Dad?
Man.
I told you your father
would never get up on us.
Never.
Hey!
I actually...
You know, Sid, you're not such a screw-up.
Ah, really?
Really?
You're a hero.
You too, Granny.
Thanks, lady.
So, still want me on your scurvy crew?
You bet.
Welcome to our herd.
Hey, you.
I can't believe you did that for me.
Thank you.
Well, someone once told me no matter
what, you never leave a friend behind.
All this sweetness is gonna rot my teeth.
If I had any.
Our home is gone.
Where do we go now?
Oh, Mama loves you too.
Yeah.
I can't wait to check this place out.
Excuse me.
Dad.
When you two get off this ship,
I expect you both to have fun.
Huh?
You're a brave kid, Wiener.
Wait.
What?
You heard me.
You two should go out and explore.
Go where the day takes you.
But be back before sunset.
Our after sunset?
Yeah, not a minute later.
Deal.
I love you, Dad.
Hey, okay, if we hang with you guys, sure.
I always liked him.
Who was the hero?
Wave Elishus.
She's not my little girl anymore.
And you're both gonna be just fine.
I know.
You know, Sidney, you've
got yourself a nice family here.
A real family.
Yeah, I'm pretty lucky.
Here, chew this kiwi for me.
I never again.
Ta-da!
Huh?
Ah!
Hey, sailor.
Whoa.
Welcome, brother.
Behold, Scratlantis.
Oh!
No!
Stop!
Brother, rise above this base desire.
Be more than rodent.
We are, we are a natural
ordinary femma, monthly,
but we can all agree
that we are, we are.
Close as close can be.
We are, we are, we are.
We are.
Family.
So it's a matter of what it looks like.
We look perfect for me.
We got every kind of
love I feel so lucky indeed.
They can keep on talking.
It's a matter of me.
Because we are.
We are.
Family.
Cam and cheese.
No, we are family.
Okay, so the links in our chain make
the strings but really they make a stronger
We are, we are, not your
ordinary femma, monthly,
but we can all agree
that we are, we are.
Close as close can be.
We are.
Family.
Yes, you'll find a chase in the sun I'm never, I'm never down Lying here, staring
up and looking down I'm never, I'm never down Live forever, forever with you
around We've only just begun, hitting the tide by drones into forever Comes,
you'll find a chase in the sun They said this day would become, we were here to run
The sun, the sun, the sun, the
sun, the sun, the sun, the sun.
You're finally chasing the sun.
you
I'm sorry, I'm sorry